Guide to the Chiron Review Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- January 2016 Acquisition, circa 1900-2015; 19.01; (20 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  - Margaret Nelms - correspondence, circa 2011 (Box 135)
    Contains material regarding "From Buggies to B-52's."
  - Phil Weidman - correspondence, proof and draft, circa 2011 (Box 135)
    Contains material regarding "I Haven't Yet Opened My Eyes."
  - Tobi Cogswell - correspondence, drafts and proof, circa 2012 (Box 135)
    Contains material regarding "Lit Up."
  - Patrick Fealey - correspondence, drafts and proofs, 2013 (Box 135)
    Contains material regarding "Mostly Madly."
  - Jeff Alfier - correspondence, drafts and proofs, 2012-2013 (Box 135)
    Contains material regarding "The City Without Her."
  - Abbey #137, 2014-02 (Box 135)
  - "The Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings Journal of Florida Literature, volume XXII", 2014 (Box 135)
  - "The Tender Touch of a Leaf," by Rochelle Hole, 1976 (Box 135)
  - Prairie Connection, newspaper, 2013 (Box 135)
  - "A Tape for Milton," by Mark Sonnenfeld, Marymark Recordings, 2011 (Box 136)
    - "A Tape for Milton," by Mark Sonnenfeld, 2011; 1; 00:18:29; The program is distorted at times. (Box 148, Item barcode 39002099362700)
      Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Various photographs and photo prints, undated (Box 136)
  - A Sip of Earth, undated; 1 (Box 149)
  - Kitty Songs, undated; 1 (Box 149)
  - Piercy and Webb, undated; 1 (Box 149)
  - Piercy D. Newman, undated; 1 (Box 149)
  - Pitchfork, undated; 1 (Box 149)
  - Various photographs and photo prints, undated; (2 folders) (Box 136)
  - Marymark Press give-out sheet series, 2012 (Box 136)
  - Unidentified print-out, undated (Box 136)
  - Vintage postcards, circa 1900s-2000s; (4 folders) (Box 136)
  - Postcards, circa 1970s-1990s; (6 folders) (Box 136)
    Also includes stickers and cards.
  - "The Asshat File", circa 2014 (Box 137)
    Contains political mailers from the 2014 election.
  - "Tales of an Ancient Go-Go-Girl," by Joan Jobe Smith - correspondence, 2013-2014 (Box 137)
  - "Mel Belin - KEP", 2014 (Box 137)
    Contains a draft of "Burglar in Brooklyn."
  - "Mean Old World: Incursions, excerpted from "Persona(e)," by John Jacob, circa 2015 (Box 137)
    Contains photocopies, correspondence, and drafts.
  - Chiron Review - correspondence, 2014-2015; (4 folders) (Box 137)
    - City Council Meeting, Harper Kansas, 2014-06-09; 1 (Box 149)
  - Chiron Review business, 2011 (Box 137)
  - "Poetry Rendezvous, Taos, New Mexico", 2014 (Box 137)
    - Poetry Rendezvous - St. John, Kansas & Taos, New Mexico, 2013-2014; 1 (Box 149)
  - Rosalea Hostetler and Prairie Connection, 2014 (Box 137)
    Contains correspondence, drafts and a newspaper.
  - Poetry Rendezvous, 2015 (Box 137)
    Contains clippings, correspondence, and various manuscript material.
  - Marymark Press give-out sheet, bookmark and "The Centaur in the Garden" print-outs, circa 2012 (Box 137)
  - Postcard correspondence, 1998-2014 (Box 138)
  - "Pauley addition, Big Horn County, Wyoming," record of survey, 2015 (Box 138)
  - Michael Hathaway - correspondence, 2000-2015; (6 folders) (Box 138)
    Contains drafts and writings.
  - "Stafford County History" - playing cards, undated (Box 138)
  - Prairie Connection, newspaper, 2015 (Box 138)
  - "#99 Chiron Review," original typescript, 2015 (Box 138)
    Contains correspondence.
  - "#100 Chiron Review," original typescript, 2015 (Box 138)
  - "#101 Chiron Review," original typescript, 2015 (Box 138)
  - Chiron Review, pen, undated (Box 138)
  - Printed material, circa 2010-2012 (Box 139)
    Contains various printed ephemera.
  - "Heritage Tours," button and note, undated (Box 139)
  - Art of Survival, proof and drafts, circa 2014 (Box 139)
  - Of Dogs and Heaven, proof, circa 2012 (Box 139)
  - "Dear Editor...," New Yorker letter and cartoon, 2015 (Box 140)
  - DNA, magazine, 2015 (Box 140)
  - "Common Sexual Deviations Explained," by Joseph Priddy - submission to Chiron Review, 2015 (Box 140)
  - Marc Bolan - Purple Prince of Pleasure, photocopies, circa 1977 (Box 140)
  - "A Garden of Storms," by Don Gaddis, typescript and correspondence, 2014 (Box 140)
  - "An Encyclopedia of Male Homosexual Poetry, Paul Knobel," note, 2011 (Box 140)
    - "An Encyclopedia of Male Homosexual Poetry, Paul Knobel", 2011; 1 (Box 149)
  - Prairie Connection, newspaper, 2014-2015 (Box 140)
  - Carnivàle, series concept and background, by Daniel Knauf, typescript, circa 2000 (Box 140)
  - Printed material and political advertisments, circa 2014 (Box 140)
  - A.B.A.T.E. of Kansas, including "Prairie Perennial Official Newsletter", 2014 (Box 140)
  - Printed material and correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 140)
  - Political pamphlet - Kansas Republican Party (Anti-Greg Orman), 2014 (Box 140)
  - Empty envelope - Steven and Mary Sassmann, 2012 (Box 140)
  - Rural Messenger, newspaper, 2012 (Box 141)
  - Donna Lane, email correspondence, 2012 (Box 141)
  - "What I Can Tell You," by Ruth Moon Kempher - manuscript, circa 2013 (Box 141)
  - Invoices and receipts - Chiron Review, 2013 (Box 141)
  - Extras Pictures for "Of Dogs", circa 2012 (Box 141)
  - "Of Dogs and Heaven," by Ruth Moon Kempher - draft, 2012 (Box 141)
  - "Of Dogs and Heaven, etc...," by Ruth Moon Kempher - draft, circa 2012 (Box 141)
  - Reciepts - Chiron Review, circa 2012 (Box 141)
  - Mailing envelopes [empty], 2012-2013 (Box 141)
  - "A Sip of Earth (proof)," drafts and Don Gaddis correspondence, circa 2011 (Box 141)
  - [untitled], undated; 1 (Box 149)
  - Belfast Imagined, 2010; 1 (Box 149)
  - "Patty Lou Goes to Rutabaga Rose's Family Reunion," by Ruth Moon Kempher and Wayne Hogan, 2011 (Box 141)
  - "The Secret Places," by Sally Page Hughes - drafts and correspondence, circa 2011 (Box 141)
  - "The Gathering Light at San Cataldo," by Jeffrey C. Alfier - drafts and correspondence, 2011 (Box 141)
  - "Being Here," by Joan Payne Kincaid - printed copy and draft, circa 2012 (Box 141)
  - "Thorns Against the Sky," by Darla McBride - correspondence and draft, 2012 (Box 141)
  - "Logic's Narrative," by Maurice Watson - correspondence and draft, 2012 (Box 141)
  - Tennessee Williams Festival, Clarksdale, Mississippi, 2014 (Box 141)
  - "Behind the Lecter," by Hal J. Daniel III, circa 2015 (Box 141)
  - #98 Chiron Review, original typescripts, 2014 (Box 142)
  - #97 Chiron Review, original typescripts, 2014; (3 folders) (Box 142)
  - "Heart Like a Hammer," by Michael Xavier - typescripts, 2014; (2 folders) (Box 142)
  - Annual Report of the Isthmian Canal Commission for the Fiscal Year Ending June 30 1911 (Box 142)
  - Various newspapers, 2013-2015; (2 folders) (Box 142)
  - John Jacob - printed material, typescripts and correspondence, circa 2009-2015 (Box 142)
  - Stafford County (Kansas) Historical Society, circa 2001 (Box 142)
  - "An Interview with Nikola Tesla, Electric Wizard," photocopy, circa 2015 (Box 142)
  - "Kingdom of the Antichrist," by Doug Clark and the Amazing Prophecy Ministry, circa 1970s; 1 (Box 143 (Record album storage))
  - The American Poetry Review, 2009 (Box 144)
  - Boston Review, 2010 (Box 144)
  - Boston Review, 2010 (Box 144)
  - "Reinvention Poetry," by Steven Sassmann, "Thank You Card," by David [?], and unframed poetry quote, by Steven Sassmann, undated (Box 145)
  - The Whole Earth Catalog, 1971 (Box 146 (oversize))
  - "A Sip of Earth, poems by Don Gaddis," cover proof, undated (Box 146 (oversize))
  - "Men Are Predictable," by K. Andrew Turner - mechanical proof, circa 2011 (Box 147 (oversize))
  - "Bland Fathomless Contempt," by Michael Xavier - mechanical proof, circa 2013 (Box 147 (oversize))
  - Tennessee Williams, poster, 1995 (Box 147 (oversize))